A Guide to the Papers and Photographs of Jackson Davis 1906-1947, and n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers and Photographs of Jackson Davis 1906-1947, and n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
3072, 3072-a
The collection is ca. 38 1/2 feet.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Charles Langhorne and Mrs. Helen Lynch, Dec. 7, 1948 and Nov. 3, 1949.
Alternative Form
The photographs, photographic negatives and glass lantern slides are available as digital images, online at https://small.library.virginia.edu/collections/featured/jackson-davis-collection-of-african-american-educational-photographs/
Biographical/Historical Information
Jackson Davis was born in Cumberland County, Virginia, on September 25, 1882, the son of William Anderson and Sally Wyatt (Guy) Davis. He attended the public schools of Richmond, Virginia, and received his B. A. from the College of William and Mary in 1902 and his M. A. from Columbia University in 1908. Honorary L.L.D. degrees were conferred upon him by the University of Richmond in 1930 and the College of William and Mary in 1931.
Following graduation from William and Mary he was the principal of the public schools of Williamsburg, Virginia. He was assistant secretary of the Roanoke, Virginia YMCA from 1903- 1904, was principal of the public schools of Marion, Virginia from 1904-1905, and was superintendent of schools in Henrico County, Virginia from 1905-1909. From 1909-1910 he was a member of the state board of examiners and inspectors of the Virginia State Board of Education, and from 1910-1915 he was state agent for African-American rural schools for the Virginia State Department of Education. In 1915 he became affiliated with the General Education Board in New York, New York, as a field agent. Two years later he was transferred to New York city as the board's general field agent, in which capacity he remained until 1929 when he was made assistant director. He became associate director in 1933 and vice-president and director in 1946. Throughout his career Davis specialized in Southern education, interracial problems, and education in Belgian Congo and Liberia. In 1935 he went to Africa as a Carnegie visitor, and in 1944 went again as head of a group sent by the Foreign Missions Conference of North America, the British Conference of Missions, and the Phelps- Stokes Fund. Davis was also a trustee of the Phelps-Stokes Fund, an organization devoted to African-American education and race relations both in America and in Africa. He became vice president of the fund in 1940, and succeeded Anson Phelps Stokes as president in 1946. During the years of his association with the General Education Board its work was concentrated on education in the Southern states and Davis' influence on behalf of better relations and understanding between whites and African-Americans and his pioneer work in promoting regional centers of education in the South were of immense significance. At the time of his death he was president of the board of trustees of Booker T. Washington Institute in Libera, president of the New York State Colonization Society, and a member of the Commission on Interracial Cooperation and of the Advisory Committee on Education in Liberia. He served as a member of the board of visitors of the College of William and Mary during 1913-1920 and as secretary of the International Education Board from 1923- 1938. Davis and Margaret Wong co-authored Africa Advancing in 1946, a book providing the results of the survey made in 1944; he was also a frequent contributor to educational journals.
Davis was a member of the Sons of the American Revolution, Virginia Academy of Science, Virginia Historical Society, Phi Beta Kappa, Theta Delta Chi, Phi Delta Kappa, and the Town Hall and Century clubs. He was married in Bluffton, Georgia, on May 9, 1911, to Corinne Mansfield ( -1941), and they had two daughters, Helen Mansfield who married John Phillip Lynch, Jr., and Ruth Elizabeth, who married Charles Rolfe Langhorne. Davis died in Cartersville, Virginia, on April 15, 1947.
Scope and Content Information
The papers consist of topical files, personal, professional, and financial files, photographs, glass lantern slides, photographic slides, negatives, card indexes and printed materials.
Arrangement
Arrangement
Papers and slides are arranged alphabetically by subject for collection 3072. Items in 3072 (negatives and slides) are arranged numerically according to slide/negative number.
Organization
The contents list is arranged by box number with the addition of the letter, "a" to the boxes from collection 3072-a (slides, lantern slides, negatives).
Contents List
- Papers 1906-1947, n.d., 13 Boxes
  Alphabetical by subject
  - Louis M. and Bertha Anderson 1941-1943 (Box 1)
  - Alexander W. Armour 1937-1947, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Trevor Arnett (1870-1955): 1920-1942, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - H. Percy Baler 1938 (Box 1)
  - Nelle Barmore 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - Robert Emory Blackwell (1854-1938): 1923-1934 (Box 1)
  - "A Book of Friendship" dedicated to Jackson Davis 1937 (Box 1)
  - Bettina Rhett Borie 1942-1946 (Box 1)
  - Walter Russell Bowie (1882-1969): 1938-1943 (Box 1)
  - William W. Brierley 1941-1946 (Box 1)
  - B. C. Caldwell 1939-1940, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Century Association 1944-1945 (Box 1)
  - Harry Woodburn Chase (1883-1955): 1945-1946 (Box 1)
  - James Saxon Childers (1899-1965): 1937-1940 (Box 1)
  - The Club 1942-1945 (Box 1)
  - Condolences 1942-1947, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - T. D. Cranston 1939-1946 (Box 1)
  - Louise Harris Curd 1938 (Box 1)
  - Rebecca Evelyn Davis 1941-1942 (Box 2)
  - James Hardy Dillard (1856-1940): 1927-1941 (Box 2)
  - J. Curtis Dixon 1939-1946 (Box 2)
  - Joseph Dupuy Eggleston (1867-1953): 1941-1946 (Box 2)
  - Leo Mortimer Favrot (1874- ): 1938-1947, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - I. Derrell Felder 1938-1942 (Box 2)
  - Abraham Flexner (1866-1959): 1938-1941 (Box 2)
  - Paul Breck Foreman (1911- ): 1940-1942 (Box 2)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman (1886-1963): 1939-1945 (Box 2)
  - Francis Pendleton Gaines (1892-1963): 1946 (Box 2)
  - Bennette Eugene Geer (1873-1964): 1940 (Box 2)
  - General Education Board 1910 (1924-1927), n.d., 2 folders (Box 2)
  - General Education Board: African Colonies 1943-1947 (Box 2)
  - General Education Board: Interviews 1937-1945 (Box 2)
  - Georgia, University System of 1941 (Box 2)
  - James Edgar Gregg (1875-1946): 1938-1942 (Box 2)
  - Hampden-Syndey College 1941-1944 (Box 3)
  - Hampton Institute 1937-1944, 5 folders (Box 3)
  - Hampton Institute: General Education Board Interviews 1939-1943 (Box 3)
  - Hampton Institute: Reports to the Board of Trustees 1943 (Box 3)
  - Hampton Institute: Personal 1943 (Box 3)
  - William Thomas Hedges (1881-1947): 1938-1947, 5 folders (Box 3)
  - Julius Rosewald Fund, Nashville 1938-1941 (Box 3)
  - Edna Rendall Kraft 1943-1944 (Box 3)
  - John Little 1937 (Box 4)
  - Charles Templeman Loram (1879-1940): 1933-1937, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - William Arthur and Susie Warner Maddox 1942-1947 (Box 4)
  - Ward N. and Miriam C. Madison 1942-1943 (Box 4)
  - Albert Russell Mann (1880-1947): 1937-1946 (Box 4)
  - Randolph and Douglas W. Maynard 1940-1943 (Box 4)
  - James Ross McCain (1881-1965): 1938-1945 (Box 4)
  - Fred McCuistion 1940-1947 (Box 4)
  - Edward G. McGehee, Jr. 1940-1944 (Box 4)
  - Francis Pickens Miller (1895-1978): 1940-1944 (Box 4)
  - Robert Russa Moton (1867-1940): 1916 (1924-1943), 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Mary Cooke Branch Mumford (Mrs. Beverley Bland Mumford) (1865-1938): 1925-1937 (Box 4)
  - Marcus Cicero Stephens Noble, Jr. (1855-1942): 1938-1941 (Box 4)
  - Omega Delta Chi Convention 1930 (Box 4)
  - Frederick Douglas Patterson (1901-1988): 1938-1943 (Box 4)
  - Personal 1930-1947 (Box 4)
  - Personal: Alabama Properties 1939-1946 (Box 4)
  - Personal: Appointments and Invitations 1937-1946 (Box 4)
  - Personal: Associates A-Z 1933-1947 (Box 4)
  - Personal: Church 1938-1947 (Box 4)
  - Personal: Contributions 1938-1947 (Box 4)
  - Personal: Family 1906 (1920-1946), n.d., 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Personal: Family Photographs 1922-1942, n.d. (Box 5)
  - Personal Financial 1937-1947 (Box 5)
  - Personal: Gifts and Thank yous 1937-1947 (Box 5)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund 1941-1945 (Box 5)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1937-1946, n.d., 5 folders (Box 5)
  - Phi Beta Kappa: Key Reporter 1941-1946 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Estelle Randolph 1933-1942, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Recommendations 1937-1944 (Box 6)
  - Richmond Hospital Service Association 1936-1940 (Box 6)
  - John Davidson Rockefeller, Jr. (1874-1960): 1939-1943 (Box 6)
  - Wickliffe Rose (1862-1931): 1939 (Box 6)
  - Rural Electrification Adminstration 1938-1941 (Box 6)
  - William Thomas Sanger (1885-1975): 1937-1946 (Box 6)
  - Gordon Grady Singleton (1890- ): 1937-1947 (Box 6)
  - Mary Phlegar Smith 1940-1947 (Box 6)
  - Speeches: Associations and Conferences 1929-1946 (Box 6)
  - Speeches: Colleges and Universities 1939-1944 (Box 6)
  - Speeches: Commencement Addresses 1941-1945 (Box 6)
  - Speeches: Founders' Day and Inaugural Addresses 1937-1946 (Box 6)
  - Speeches: Travel Impressions 1942, n.d. (Box 6)
  - Tenessee Colleges and Universities 1939-1947 (Box 7)
  - Theta Delta Chi 1937-1945, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Halsten Joseph Thorkelson (1875- ): 1926 (1944-1946) (Box 7)
  - Town Hall Club 1931-1939 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1937-1946 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Commission on Interracial Cooperation 1937-1944 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Education Commission 1944-1945, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Virginia, University of 1937-1946 (Box 7)
  - William and Mary, College of 1937-1946, 5 folders (Box 7-8)
    1937-July 1942 Box 7 (3 folders)
    1942- August 1946 Box 8 (2 folders)
  - William and Mary, College of: Alumni Association 1924-1944 (Box 8)
  - William and Mary, College of: Associations Incorporate and Bylaws 1939 (Box 8)
  - William and Mary, College of: Printed 1937-1944 (Box 8)
  - Elizabeth "Bessie" M. Williamson 1937-1943 (Box 8)
  - Arthur Davis Wright (1885-1947): 1937-1946, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Writings on Education 1925-1928, n.d., 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Writings on Education: Notes 1920-1930s (Box 8)
  - Writings on Religious and Social Issues n.d. (Box 8)
- Photographs 1917-1947, n.d. (Box 9-11)
  The 6000 number series are prints for which there are no negatives.
  Photographs are arranged alphabetically by subject
  - Photographs Identified
    - Africa 1944, n.d., 6291-6303; 14 photographs (Box 9)
      Liberia, unidentified
    - Alabama 1922, n.d., 6127-6129, 6168-6195; 36 photographs, 11 postcards (Box 9)
      Bibb County, Birmingham, Coosa County, Fort Deposit, Lowndes County, Montgomery County, Selma, Tuscaloosa, Tuskegee Institute; Selma and Tuskegee postcards
    - Arkansas n.d., 6227 (Box 9)
      Edmondson
    - Florida 1925, n.d., 6228-6242; 23 photographs (Box 9)
      Daytona, Gainesville, Leesburg, Miami, Palm Beach County, St. Augustine, Sarasota, Tallahassee
    - Georgia n.d., 6243-6349; 8 photographs (Box 9)
      Coweta County, Thunderbolt, Waycross
    - Indiana n.d., 6250 (Box 9)
    - Kansas n.d. (Box 9)
    - Kentucky 1919-1928, n.d., 6251-6253; 16 photographs (Box 9)
      Burgin, Danville, Harrodsburg, Louisville, Madisonville, Paducah, unidentified
    - Louisiana 1917-1921, n.d., 6142-6165; 62 photographs, 12 postcards (Box 9)
      Bastrop, Baton Rouge, Bienville, Calcasieu, East Carroll, Lake Charles, Ruston, Sabria Nor?, Tangipahoa, Terrebonne, Theriot, Washington, Welsh, unidentified; Baton Rouge postcards
    - Maryland 1921, 6068-6070; 8 photographs (Box 9)
      Baltimore, Prince George County, unidentified
    - Mississippi 1917-1926, n.d., 6000, 6009-6049, 6057-6061, 6311-6314, 6050, 6052-6053, 6056, 6062-6067, 6114-6120; 2 folders--159 photographs, 2 postcards (Box 9)
      Alcorn, Braxton, Coahoma County, Columbia, Covington County, Edwards, Ellisville, Forest County, Hattiesburg, Jackson, Lamar County, Leland, Mound Bayou, Okolona, Pearl River County, Starksville, Tougaloo, Tupelo, Utica, Wiggins; unidentified numbered; unidentified; Gulfport postcards
    - New York n.d., 4 postcards (Box 9)
      Ithaca, New York, and Queensborough postcards
    - North Carolina 1917-1922, 1941, n.d., 6001-6008, 6071-6078, 6079-6098, 6100-6113, 6121, 6157, 6197-6208, 6209-6210, 6212, 6218-6225, 6304-6306, 6307-6310, 6314-6316; 2 folders--193 photographs, 1 postcard (Box 9)
      Asheville, Chapel Hill, Columbus County, Elizabeth City, Fayettevile, Greensboro, Halifax County, Kinston, Kittrell, Method, Mount Mitchell, Pamlico, Parmele, Pitt County, Raleigh, Salisbury, Seminole County, Smithfield, Wadesboro, Wake County, Winston-Salem, Winton; Stony Point; unidentified; Winston-Salem postcards
    - Oklahoma and Oregon 1919-1922, n.d., 6130-6141, 6206; 48 photographs, 2 postcards (Box 9)
      Bookertee, Carter County, Langston, Rentiesville; unidentified numbered; unidentified; Muskogee postcards; Portland (Oregon) postcards
    - South Carolina 1920-1931, n.d., 6262-6290, 6315-6317; 2 folders--105 photographs, 23 postcards (Box 9)
      Allendale, Bamberg, Cola, Columbia, Conway, Greenville County, Hartsville, Laurens County, Marion, Mayesville, Moncks Corner, Orangeburg, Ridge Spring, St. Helena Island, Sumter, Trenton, Williamsburg County; unidentified; Charleston and St. Helena Island postcards
    - Tennessee 1921, 1930, n.d., 6226, 6236, 6254-6259, 6211, 6213, 6217, 6318-6321, 6323, 6325-6327, 6329-6338; 66 photographs, 2 postcards (Box 9)
      Brownsville, Clarksville, Fayette County, Henry County, Maryville, McMinnville, Mount Meigs, Nashville, Shelby County, Signal Mountain, Wilson County; unidentified; Knoxville postcards
    - Texas 1918-1927, n.d., 2 folders--148 photographs, 6 postcards (Box-folder 10)
      Austin, Bishop, Camp County, Guadalupe, Hallettsville, Harrison County, Houston, Hunt County, Huntsville, Kerens, Ladonia, Limestone County, Manor, Marion, Marshall, McAllen, Mexia, Pittsburg, Prairie Grove, Prairie View, San Antonio, Sequin, Sweet Home, Travis County, Tyler, Waco, Walker County; unidentified; Austin postcards
    - Virginia 1913-1933, n.d., 6344, 6359, 6365, 6367, 6398, 6401-6404, 6412-6417, 6420-6445; 2 folders--172 photographs, 10 postcards (Box 10)
      Albemarle County, Alexandria, Amelia County, Amherst County, Bowling Green, Brunswick County, Burkeville, Caroline County, Charles City County, Charlottesville, Chesterfield County, Emporia, Gloucester, Halifax, Hampton, Harrisonburg, Henrico County (and "Virginia Randolph and her work"), Kenbridge, Kilmarnock, King and Queen County, King George, King William, Lawrenceville, Lottsburg, Lynchburg, Manassas, Middlesex County, New Kent County, Nottoway County, Petersburg, Rappahannock River, Richmond, Rockbridge County, Surry County, Waverly, Whitestone, Williamsburg, Winchester, York County, unidentified; Cartersville, Hampton, Lynchburg, and Petersburg postcards
    - Virginia: Halifax County n.d., photographic album of 18 photographs (Box 10)
    - Virginia: "Stingray," Saluda, Middlesex County 1934, n.d., 22 photographs (Box 10)
    - Virginia: Virginia State College Commencement 1945, 10 photographs (Box 10)
    - West Virginia 1921-1928, n.d., 7 photographs (Box 10)
      Harpers Ferry, Institute, Shepherdstown
  - Photographs Unidentified
    - People
      - People -- General Education Board n.d., 6446-6455, 6457-6463, 6464-6474, 6476-6508, 6512-6516, 6517-6521, 6523-6558, 6560-6563, 6565-6571; 3 folders--131 photographs (Box 10)
        members and related --one person, --two people, --three people, --four people, --five or six people, --six or more people
      - People -- General Education Board and State Agents Negro Rural Schools 1929, 1939, n.d., 12 photographs (Box 10)
        G. E. B. members, including Trevor Arnett and Wallace Buttrick; Meeting of the State Agents Negro Rural Schools, New Orleans, Louisiana; Ottis' Fish Market
      - People -- Children and Youths n.d., 27 photographs (Box 10)
      - People -- Children and Youths -- classrooms n.d., 30 photographs (Box 10)
      - People -- Groups -- outdoor scenes n.d., 2 folders--79 photographs (Box 10)
        outdoor scenes, --parades, --sports, --vehicles, streets
      - People -- Groups -- posed n.d., 87 photographs (Box 10)
        men; women; indoors; outdoors
      - People -- Individuals n.d., 2 folders--108 photographs (Box 10)
        --one person, --two people, --three people
    - Scenes
      - Generic, 6572-6575, 6007, 6577-6578, 6580-6488
      - Building Scenes--Churches n.d., 9 photographs (Box 11)
      - Building Scenes -- Construction n.d., 6563, 6574-6575; 16 photographs (Box 11)
      - Building Scenes -- Public Schools, Hospitals, etc. n.d., 121 photographs (Box 11)
      - Building Scenes -- Residences and other n.d., 6559, 6576, 6579, 6592-6601; 2 folders--123 photographs (Box 11)
      - Building Scenes -- Shacks n.d., 6602-6604; 25 photographs (Box 11)
      - Building Scenes -- with children n.d., 6605-6606, 6608; 15 photographs (Box 11)
      - Building Scenes -- with large groups of people n.d., 6609-6612; 51 photographs (Box 11)
      - Building Scenes -- with small groups of people n.d., 6620-6626; 23 photographs (Box 11)
      - Farm Scenes n.d., 6630-6633; 24 photographs (Box 11)
      - Rural Scenes -- Churches and Schools (identified) n.d., 6607, 6613, 6619, 6634-6636, 6638-6640; 24 photographs (Box 11)
        Averill; Bethel Church and School; Brookville School; Cappahoocie School; Chester School; Flatiron School; Indian Road School; Pace School; Poplar School; Rising Sun School; Rising Valley Church and Schoolhouse; Swansboro School; White Oak Store; unidentified; and, Rosenwald School, the 4000th
      - Rural Scenes -- Country, Forest, Mountains, etc. n.d., 6637, 6641, 6677; 78 photographs (Box 11)
      - Rural Scenes -- Exhibits n.d., 18 photographs (Box 11)
      - Rural Scenes -- Homes (identified) n.d., 13 photographs (Box 11)
        J. H. Alston; Henry Brooks; George Calloway; H. R. Eubank; Walter Johnson; Sallie Marable; Elnora Neal; McQueen Smith; H. H. Wynn
      - Rural Scenes -- Residences and Farms n.d., 12 photographs (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous sent by W[illiam] W. [Brierly] n.d., 6521, 6531, 6570, 6678-6720, 6722, 6724, 6727-6750, 6800-6801; 28 photographs (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous numbered n.d., 4 folders--269 photographs (Box 11)
        Grouped by identifying number on verso
- Articles and Miscellaneous 1939-1945, n.d., Printed matter (Box 12)
- Bulletins, etc 1936-1943 (Box 12)
- Newspaper Clippings 1926-1947, 3 folders (Box 12)
- Address Book n.d. (Box 13)
- Checkbook: American Bank and Trust Company November 1932-December 1936, 3 folders (Box 13)
- Checkbook: Chase National Bank June 1933-June 1937, 2 folders (Box 13)
- Monthly Expense Books: Trip to Africa March 1935-August 1935 (Box 13)
- Savings Passbook: American National Bank December 1926-February 1933 (Box 13)
- Archival Prints (Box 14-28)
  These are archival prints of the negatives listed in Boxes 1a-10a
  Arranged in numerical order.
  - Prints 0000-0299 (Box 14)
  - Prints 0300-0599 (Box 15)
  - Prints 0600-0899 (Box 16)
  - Prints 0900-1199 (Box 17)
  - Prints 1200-1499 (Box 18)
  - Prints 1500-1799 (Box 19)
  - Prints 1800-2099 (Box 20)
  - Prints 2100-2399 (Box 21)
  - Prints 2400-2699 (Box 22)
  - Prints 2700-2999 (Box 23)
  - Prints 3000-5049 (Box 24)
  - Prints 5050-AO43 (Box 25)
  - Prints AP01-CC05 (Box 26)
  - Prints CD01-EF07 (Box 27)
  - Prints EG01-GM03 (Box 28)
- Numbered &Unnumbered Negatives, These negatives are bagged in groups of twenty (Box 1a-10a)
  - Negatives 0000-0419 (Box 1a)
    Missing images 0071, 0129, 0132
  - Negatives 0420-0999 (Box 2a)
    Missing images 0608-0612, 0923
  - Negatives 1000-1559 (Box 3a)
  - 1560-2039 (Box 4a)
    Missing image 1797
  - Negatives 2040-2549 (Box 5a)
    Missing images 2332, 2326-29, 2523
  - Negatives 2550-3119 (Box 6a)
    Missing images 2705-2713
  - Negatives 3120-AO32 (Box 7a)
    Missing images 3127, 3129, 3210-12, 3249
  - Negatives AO33-EA03 (Box 8a)
  - Negatives EA04-IA06 (Box 9a)
  - Extra Glass Slides (Box 10a)
    - Series H (Box 10a)
      NP-157.HA: Group photo
      NP-157.HB: Woman in kitchen
      NP-157.HC: Building
      NP-157.HD: Church
      NP-157.HE: Buildings
      NP-157.HF: Building
      NP-157.HG: School house
      NP-157.HH: School building
      NP-157.HI:
      NP-157.HJ: School building
      NP-157.HK: School building
      NP-157.HL: Building
      NP-157.HM: School building
      NP-157.HN: Group of men
      NP-157.HO: Two men
      NP-157.HP: Group of men
      NP-157.HQ: Group of school girls
      NP-157.HR: Building
      NP-157.HS: Group of Students
    - Series I (Box 10a)
      NP-157.IA01: Perce Rock, Gaspé Bay
      NP-157.IA02
      NP-157.IA03
      NP-157.IA04
      NP-157.IA05
      NP-157.IA06
- Glass Lantern Slides, 224 individual slides. (Box 12a-15a)
  Note: the numerical order of the 3072-a boxes are not continuous since the materials are stored in different locations. There is no Box 11a
  Slides are arranged chronologically by slide identification number.
  - Labelled Slides (Box 12a-13a)
    - Slides of Southern Schools, L-1151 - L-1202 (Box 12a-13a)
      - Lowndes County Training School; Charity, Alabama, L-1151 (Box 12a)
      - Tuscaloosa Co. Training School; Tuscaloosa, Ala., L-1152 (Box 12a)
      - Vocational Agriculture School; Bruns, Alabama, L-1153 (Box 12a)
      - Industrial Building; Fordyce, Arkansas, L-1154 (Box 12a)
      - Lee County Training School; Marianna, Arkansas, L-1155 (Box 12a)
      - Teachers at Palm Beach (Fla) Co Training School, L-1156 (Box 12a)
      - Palm Beach County Training School, Florida, L-1157 (Box 12a)
      - Clarke CTS (Ga): Chancellor Barrow, Others 1922, L-1158 (Box 12a)
      - Clarke County (Georgia) Training School Kitchen, L-1159 (Box 12a)
      - Teacher's House; Washington C.T.S. (Georgia), L-1160 (Box 12a)
      - Washington C.T.S.; Sandersville, Georgia, L-1161 (Box 12a)
      - Washington C.T.S.; Sandersville, Georgia, L-1162 (Box 12a)
      - Bouroon County Training School; Kentucky, L-1163 (Box 13a)
      - Graduating Class, Morhouse P.T.S., Louisiana, L-1164 (Box 13a)
      - Morhouse Parish Training School, Louisiana, L-1165 (Box 13a)
      - Old Church used as School;Milliken's Bend, Louisiana, L-1166 (Box 13a)
      - Rosewald School; Milliken's Bend, Louisiana, L-1167 (Box 13a)
      - New Industrial Building;Hathesburg, Mississippi, L-1168 (Box 13a)
      - Lee County Training School; Tupelo, Miss. 1921, L-1169 (Box 13a)
      - Harry County Training School; Conway, S.C., L-1170 (Box 13a)
      - Rosewald School; Hartsville, South Carolina 1920, L-1171 (Box 13a)
      - Superintendents in Winston-Salem, S.C. 1919, L-1172 (Box 13a)
      - Fayette Co. Training School; Somerville, Tenn, L-1173 (Box 13a)
      - Old School; Somerville, Tennessee, L-1174 (Box 13a)
      - Wilson County Training School; Lebanon, Tenn 1919, L-1175 (Box 13a)
      - Haywood Co. Training School; Brownsville, Tenn, L-1176 (Box 13a)
      - Rosenwald School; Gregg County, Texas 1921, L-1177 (Box 13a)
      - Travis C.T.S. (Old Building) Manor, Texas, L-1178 (Box 13a)
      - Travis County Training School; Manor, Texas, L-1179 (Box 13a)
      - New Graded School Oak Grove #2; Brunswick Co., Virginia, L-1180 (Box 13a)
      - Old School #1; Oak Grove, Brunswick Co., Va., L-1181 (Box 13a)
      - Capilarry School (Virginia) Physics Class, L-1182 (Box 13a)
      - Carolina, Va: W. Baylor, Sup't Washington, L-1183 (Box 13a)
      - Charles City County (Va) Training School, L-1184 (Box 13a)
      - Caroline County (Va) Training School, 1921, L-1185 (Box 13a)